vovici.net 2010-12-25

# Privacy Policy | Vovici

Vovici Corporation (Vovici) is committed to safe guarding the privacy of our users' information. We have established this privacy statement to demonstrate our firm commitment to online privacy. This privacy statement applies exclusively to the Web site [www.vovici.com](http://www.vovici.com/ "www.vovici.com") . Information obtained from visitors and customers will only be used for internal purposes. Vovici Corporation at no time shall sell, rent, or otherwise share your personal information with any third parties for their promotional purposes. Vovici Corporation is a Licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy program. TRUSTe is an independent organization whose mission is to build users' trust and confidence in the internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. Vovici has elected to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe as a testament of our commitment to your privacy. 

**Contact Information  
**When you register with us, we require that you provide correct contact information, which may include your name, email address, phone number, and other types of information. The information you provide allows us to send you periodic reminders about your account status and contact you regarding technical issues. If you register with Vovici in error, please contact us and we will delete your record from our database. 

You may contact Vovici concerning this privacy policy and our privacy practices at the following: 

**Mailing Address:**  
Vovici Corporation  
45365 Vintage Park Plaza  
Ste 250  
Dulles, Virginia 20166 USA

| 

**Phone Numbers:**  
1.800.941.0904  
+1.703.481.9326

**Email Address:**  
  
---|---  
  
We **do not sell, share, or distribute any information** you provide during the registration process or in discussions with our survey advisors. Additionally, we use a double opt-in registration process to further assure the security of your contact information. Any attempt to circumvent or abuse our system through multiple registrations, entering someone else's contact information or falsifying any data will result in immediate deletion of any and all records and accounts for that user.

In the event that your inquiry goes unaddressed within a reasonable time expectation, or hasn't been addressed to your satisfaction, please contact [TRUSTe](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint&url= "TRUSTe") who shall then work as a liaison in assisting us to resolve your concerns.

**Safe Harbor  

**Newsletters  
**When you provide your email address to receive our newsletter or indicate on your registration form that you would like to receive our newsletter, we will use your email address to send our newsletter. You may opt-out of receiving our newsletter at any time by following the unsubscribe instructions provided with it, updating your user profile, or by contacting the Vovici Webmaster via email at [privacy@vovici.com](mailto:privacy@vovici.com "privacy@vovici.com"). We will process your request as soon as possible.

**Tell-A-Friend Email  
**If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. Vovici does not store this information, or use it for any other purposes beyond those disclosed above.

We also provide widgets on the Web site to users as a courtesy allowing you to share data on third party platforms. These widgets do not collect, or store any of your personal information submitted to us on the Web site.

**Requesting/Updating Your Information  
**Registered users with Vovici may request a copy of their information on file with Vovici by contacting the company via phone at 1.800.941.0904 or +1.703.481.9326.

Registered users may update their information on file with Vovici by either a) contacting Vovici at the phone numbers listed above, or b) filling out a form on the Web site with their new contact information within their account settings. 

**Log Files  
**As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp and clickstream data.

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.

We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information.

**Cookies  
**A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.

We use both temporary and persistent cookies to maintain your session with our website and provide website usage statics. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's "help" file. More information about cookie technology can be found on the Microsoft® website at: <http://www.microsoft.com/info/cookies.mspx>.

If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as contests or surveys, will be limited. As some of our promotions or surveys may be targeted towards responses to a particular marketing program, if the persistent cookie for that program is not present due to visitor deletion, you may not be invited to participate in the corresponding survey or promotion. We may also employ the use of one pixel images embedded within our web pages (web beacons) to track and analyze user preferences and page traffic in improving our offerings. These images are not tied to personal information.

Third Party Cookies: We may from time to time employ the services of a third party agent in tracking non-personal, statistical and aggregated data about our user base. This third party agent may make use of cookies and web beacons to which Vovici has no access to this end. We use this information to understand and improve our Web site offerings.

**Security Measures  
**If you have questions about security on our Web site, you can send us an email at [privacy@vovici.com](mailto:privacy@vovici.com "privacy@vovici.com").

**Surveys  
**When you publish your survey on our servers, we will provide you with a unique URL to display your survey. We will not provide this URL to any other person or entity, but we will provide your survey to any web browser requesting your unique URL. We may review your survey contents for violations of our Use Policy. If we determine your survey is in violation of our Use Policy, we will attempt to contact you and reserve the right to delete your survey and results from our systems.

**Survey Results  
**It's your data. We will not attempt to read your survey results at any time unless explicitly instructed to do so by you, except that, solely with respect to any use of the EFM for CRM Module, we do review, process and provide analysis in aggregate form with respect to the results of specific format questions developed by Vovici regarding the likelihood of a survey respondent to refer others to the applicable products and/or services of an organization. We only disclose this information in aggregate form with respect to the survey results to these questions for the applicable organization for the EFM for CRM Module and not in any way that personally identifies you or your specific response to the questions in the survey. We do not own the contents of the data for your survey. Except for the limited analysis performed by us on the specific responses to the EFM for CRM Module, we only have access to your surveys for purposes of backup and troubleshooting. When your survey results are received by us, we will store them in a secure location. We will only allow your survey results to be downloaded directly into our desktop software or accessed through our online web interface. We have security measures in place to protect your results while stored on our servers and we will prosecute any attempt to access this information without authorization to the fullest extent of the law.

**E-Mail Notification System  
**Our e-mail notification system stores your e-mail addresses on our server in a secured location. These e-mail addresses are kept on the server for tracking and click notification purposes. Much like survey data, these addresses are yours, not the property of Vovici Corporation. Vovici technical support and development may examine these lists for support and troubleshooting purposes. We will not use or sell these e-mail addresses to anyone; any attempt to access your e-mail addresses without your authorization will be prosecuted to the fullest extent of the law.

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here or by means of a notice.

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Website, please feel free to contact us through the contact information listed at the top of this page.

We post customer testimonials on the Web site. These testimonials may on occasion include the user's name. We obtain our users' consent to include this personal information with their testimonial prior to posting on our Web site.
